Register of the Stanislaw Mikolajczyk Papers, 1899-1966
Hoover Institution Archives
- INTERNATIONAL PEASANT UNION FILE, 1948-1966
  - Chairman
    - Correspondence
      - 1954
        - January-June (Folder 4)
        - July-December (Folder 5)
      - 1955 (Folder 6)
      - 1956
        - January-June (Folder 7)
        - July-December (Folder 8)
      - 1957
        - January-June (Folder 9)
        - July-December (Folder 10)
      - 1958
        - January-June (Folder 11)
        - July-December (Folder 12)
      - 1959
        - January-June (Folder 13)
        - July-December (Folder 14)
      - 1960
        - January-June (Box 127, Folder 1)
        - July-December (Folder 2)
      - 1961
        - January-June (Folder 3)
        - July-December (Folder 4)
      - 1962
        - January-June (Folder 5)
        - July-December (Folder 6)
      - 1963
        - January-June (Folder 7)
        - July-December (Folder 8)
      - 1964
        - January-June (Folder 9)
        - July-December (Folder 10)
    - Interviews, 1958 (Folder 11)
    - Speeches
      - 1955 (Folder 12)
      - 1956 (Folder 13)
      - 1957 (Folder 14)
      - 1958 (Folder 15)
      - 1961 (Folder 16)
    - Statements
      - 1957 (Folder 17)
      - 1958 (Folder 18)
    - Writings
      - 1955 (Folder 19)
      - 1956 (Folder 20)
      - 1957 (Folder 21)
      - 1958 (Folder 22)
      - 1961 (Folder 23)
  - Commission on Internal Affairs and Agrarian Problems- Collectivization problems. Reports, 1951 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Congresses
    - First, Washington, 1948
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Agenda (Folder 3)
      - By-laws (Folder 4)
      - Program and objectives (Folder 5)
      - Report (Folder 6)
      - Statute (Folder 7)
    - Second, Washington, 1950
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Summary of first two congresses (Folder 9)
    - Third, Washington, 1952
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Agenda (Folder 11)
      - Biographies of participants (Folder 12)
      - Central Committee file (Folder 13)
      - Correspondence
        - 1951 November-December (Folder 14)
        - 1952
          - January-April (Folder 15)
          - April-May (Folder 16)
          - May-November (Folder 17)
      - Member organizations file (Folder 18)
      - Protocol (Folder 19)
      - Proceedings (Folder 20)
      - Report (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Speeches
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 2)
        - Popiel, Karol (Folder 3)
    - Fourth, New York, 1954
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Appeals and resolutions (Folder 5)
      - Invitations and responses (Folder 6)
      - Minutes (Folder 7)
      - Reports (Folder 8)
      - Speeches
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 10)
    - Fifth, Paris, 1956
      - Invitations
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Corps diplomatique (Folder 12)
        - France (Folder 13)
        - Individuals (Folder 14)
      - Minutes (Folder 15)
      - Press file
        - General (Box 130, Folder 1)
        - Releases (Folder 2)
      - Reports
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Member parties
          - English edition (Folder 4)
          - French edition (Folder 5)
        - Peasants and communism (Folder 6)
      - Resolutions (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Speeches
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 3)
    - Sixth, Washington, 1959
      - General
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Greetings and messages (Folder 5)
        - Press releases (Folder 6)
        - Proceedings (Folder 7)
        - Reports (Folder 8)
        - Speeches
          - General (Folder 9)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 10)
      - Central Committee (Folder 11)
      - Commissions (Folder 12)
      - Delegates (Folder 13)
      - Member parties (Folder 14)
    - Seventh, Washington, 1961
      - General (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Invitations. Includes letter to John F. Kennedy (Folder 2)
      - Lists of delegates
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Polish (Folder 4)
      - Press reports (Folder 5)
      - Program (Folder 6)
      - Reference materials (Folder 7)
      - Reports
        - General (Folder 8)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 9)
      - Resolutions (Folder 10)
      - Speeches
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Folder 12)
    - Eighth, Washington, 1964
      - Communiqués (Folder 13)
      - Messages from the United States government (Folder 14)
      - Proceeding transcripts from tape (Folder 15)
      - Program (Folder 16)
      - Reports (Folder 17)
      - Resolutions (Folder 18)
      - Speeches - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 19)
  - Cooperating organizations
    - African and Asian Nations Confederation - Conference, Bandung, 1955. Contains letter from Mohammad Ali, Prime Minister of Pakistan (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Assembly of Captive European Nations, I.P.U.'s involvement in, 1955 (Folder 2)
    - Catholic Rural Life - Congresses
      - First, Castel Gandolfo, Italy, 1951 June 25-July 1 (Folder 3)
      - Fourth, Santiago, Chile, 1957 April 1-6
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Organizational principles file (Folder 5)
        - Participants file
          - General (Folder 6)
          - Business cards (Folder 7)
        - Press clippings
          - Chilean (Folder 8)
          - Polish émigré (Folder 9)
        - Program (Folder 10)
        - Report (Folder 11)
        - Speeches
          - General (Folder 12)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 13)
    - Central and East European Union, 1953-1954 (Folder 14)
    - Christian Democratic Union of Central Europe - Congress, First, New York, 1953 March 13-15 (Folder 15)
    - Council of Europe, 1952-1953. Includes resolution no. 22 (Folder 16)
    - European Confederation of Agriculture - Congresses
      - Tenth, Vienna, 1958
        - General (Box 134, Folder 1)
        - Activist lists (Folder 2)
        - Press clippings (Folder 3)
        - Proceedings (Folder 4)
        - Program (Folder 5)
        - Reports of commissions (Folder 6)
        - Resolutions (Folder 7)
        - Speeches (Folder 8)
      - Eleventh, Palermo, 1959
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Proceedings (Folder 10)
        - Program (Folder 11)
        - Reports of commissions (Folder 12)
        - Resolutions (Folder 13)
        - Speeches - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 14)
      - Twelfth, Brussels, 1960
        - General (Folder 15)
        - Communiqués (Folder 16)
        - Participant lists (Folder 17)
        - Reports of commissions (Folder 18)
        - Proceedings (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Program (Folder 2)
        - Reports (Folder 3)
        - Resolutions (Folder 4)
        - Speeches - Recordatti, A. Zappi (Folder 5)
      - Thirteenth, Baden-Baden, 1961
        - General (Folder 6)
        - Communiqués (Folder 7)
        - Proceedings (Folder 8)
        - Program (Folder 9)
      - Fourteenth, Madrid, 1962
        - General (Folder 10)
        - Declarations and resolutions (Folder 11)
        - Participant lists (Folder 12)
        - Program (Folder 13)
        - Report (Folder 14)
        - Speeches
          - General (Folder 15)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 16)
      - Fifteenth, Cannes, 1963
        - General (Folder 17)
        - Press file (Folder 18)
        - Speeches
          - General (Folder 19)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 20)
      - Seventeenth, Amsterdam, 1965 (Folder 21)
    - European Movement - Central and East European Commission
      - General
        - Europe Unité, special Strasbourg issue of European Digest, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 1)
        - Political Demands of the Workers in Eastern Europe by Paul Barton, Paris, 1957 (Folder 2)
        - "Unity of European Culture." Transcripts of B.B.C. programs, 1953 (Folder 3)
      - Conference, 1952, London
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Member lists (Folder 5)
        - Minutes
          - Part 1 (Folder 6)
          - Part 2 (Folder 7)
        - Report, "The Democratic Reconstruction of Agriculture within the Framework of a United Europe" by G. M. Dymitrov (Folder 8)
        - Resolutions
          - General
            - General (Folder 9)
            - Final (Folder 10)
          - Agricultural (Folder 11)
          - Cultural (Folder 12)
          - Economic (Folder 13)
          - Political (Folder 14)
          - Social (Folder 15)
          - Youth (Folder 16)
        - Speaker and delegate lists (Folder 17)
    - Free Europe Committee
      - Correspondence - Federation plans, 1954 (Folder 18)
      - Report, "A Report of Soviet Bloc Economic Activities in the Free World," 1955. Mimeograph (Folder 19)
    - Indépendants et Paysans - Congress, Second, 1956, Versailles
      - General (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Documents (Folder 2)
      - Press file (Folder 3)
      - Speeches (Folder 4)
    - International Federation of Agricultural Producers - Conferences
      - Fifth, Mexico City, 1951. Statements by the National Farmers Union (Folder 5)
      - Ninth, Lafayette, 1957
        - Anniversary publications (Folder 6)
        - Budgetary outlines (Folder 7)
        - Documents (Folder 8)
        - Meeting procedure file (Folder 9)
      - Tenth, Brussels, 1958
        - Auditor's report (Folder 10)
        - Constitution (Folder 11)
        - Documents
          - Part 1 (Folder 12)
          - Part 2 (Folder 13)
        - Handbooks (Box 138, Folder 1)
        - Participant lists (Folder 2)
        - Program (Folder 3)
        - Resolutions (Folder 4)
        - Soviet propaganda brochures (Folder 5)
        - Statements by various delegations (Folder 6)
    - Lincoln-Petkov Academy, "A Two-Part Plan to Correct Major Weaknesses of the Free World In the Psycho-Political War," ca. 1954. Typescript (Folder 7)
    - Mid-European Studies Center - East European Inquiry. Agricultural project, 1953 (Folder 8)
    - National Committee for a Free Europe
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Annual student conference, Third, 1953 (Folder 10)
      - Federation Group. Reports of committees on European unification, 1953
        - Agriculture (Folder 11)
        - Defense (Folder 12)
        - European Coal and Steel Community (Folder 13)
        - Finance (Folder 14)
        - Labor and social security (Folder 15)
        - Power and energy
          - General (Folder 16)
          - Central Europe (Folder 17)
        - Transport and telecommunications (Folder 18)
      - Forced Labor Camps Conference, 1953
        - General (Folder 19)
        - Agenda and participant list (Folder 20)
        - Correspondence
          - General (Folder 21)
          - Letter to Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1953 August (Folder 22)
        - Reports on various countries (Folder 23)
    - Polish Peasant Party
      - Commemorative meeting, New York, 1955 September 3 (Folder 24)
      - Party's internal situation, 1955 (Folder 25)
    - Rural Youth - International gathering, Vienna, 1954 (Folder 26)
  - Foreign sections
    - General
      - General (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Questionnaire on agricultural statistics in Eastern Europe before and after imposition of communism (Folder 2)
    - Albanian (Folder 3)
    - Asian
      - 1950. Manifesto to the Peasants of Asia (Folder 4)
      - 1951 (Folder 5)
      - 1955 (Folder 6)
      - 1957 (Folder 7)
    - Bulgarian
      - 1948 (Folder 8)
      - 1954-1963 (Folder 9)
    - Czechoslovak
      - General
        - 1948 (Folder 10)
        - 1949 (Folder 11)
        - 1950-1954. Ruzyne prison and collectivization reports (Folder 12)
        - 1954 June - Commemorative meetings, New York
          - Beran, Rudolf (Folder 13)
          - Hodza, Milan (Folder 14)
        - 1957-1964 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Agricultural statistics
        - General
          - General (Folder 2)
          - Summaries (Folder 3)
        - Crops production and forestry, 1936-1949 (Folder 4)
        - Five year plan, 1948-1953 (Folder 5)
        - Land utilization and ownership, 1933-1951 (Folder 6)
        - Livestock, 1936-1951 (Folder 7)
    - Estonian
      - 1948 (Folder 8)
      - 1949 (Folder 9)
      - 1950-1961 (Folder 10)
    - Hungarian
      - 1951-1955 (Folder 11)
      - 1956 - Events
        - General (Folder 12)
        - Response in the United States (Folder 13)
        - United Nations. General Assembly (Folder 14)
      - 1958 - Imre Nagy Forum, Georgetown University (Folder 15)
      - 1962-1963 (Folder 16)
    - Italian. Bulletins, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Lithuanian
      - General. Current News on the Lithuanian Situation, 1952-1954 (Folder 2)
      - Grinius, Kazys, Commemoration of, 1955 (Folder 3)
    - Polish
      - 1950-1952 - Polish-German relations. Reports of Polish I.P.U. representatives in Germany (Folder 4)
      - 1951-1952. Polski Zielony Nurt: Biuletyn Polskiej Sekcji Miedzynarodowej Unii Chlopskiej i Polskiego Stronnictwa Ludowego we Franfkurcie (Folder 5)
      - 1953
        - Central Europe. Report by Polish Study Group entitled "Economic Cooperation in Central and Eastern Europe" (Folder 6)
        - Polish-German post-war relations (Folder 7)
      - 1955
        - Witos, Wincenty, Commemoration of, New York (Folder 8)
        - World Festival of Youth and Students, Warsaw (Folder 9)
      - 1956 - Political conditions in Poland
        - General (Box 142, Folder 1)
        - Bulletins and newspapers (Folder 2)
      - 1957 (Folder 3)
      - 1959 (Folder 4)
      - 1960-1963 (Folder 5)
      - 1962-1966 - Polish-German border issues (Folder 6)
    - Romanian
      - 1949 (Folder 7)
      - 1955-1963 (Folder 8)
    - South American
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Manifesto to the Peasants of Central and South America, 1961 (Folder 10)
    - Ukrainian (Folder 11)
    - Yugoslav (Folder 12)
  - Forums
    - General
      - 1953, New York
        - General
          - General (Box 143, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence
            - General (Folder 2)
            - Telegrams (Folder 3)
          - Directives for Union's activities (Folder 4)
          - Invitations (Folder 5)
          - Panel conclusions
            - General (Folder 6)
            - Panel 1 (Folder 7)
            - Panel 2 (Folder 8)
          - Press file on Soviet agriculture
            - General (Folder 9)
            - Clippings (Folder 10)
          - Program (Folder 11)
          - Questionnaires (Folder 12)
          - Radio and press reports (Folder 13)
          - Reference material
            - General (Folder 14)
            - East European agriculture (Folder 15)
        - Round table forum (Box 144, Folder 1)
        - Sections
          - Czechoslovak (Folder 2)
          - Hungarian (Folder 3)
          - Slovenian (Folder 4)
        - Soviet agriculture (Folder 5)
        - Speakers
          - General
            - General (Folder 6)
            - Biographies (Folder 7)
            - Questions addressed to (Folder 8)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 9)
      - 1956 Rome (Folder 10)
      - 1958 Brussels
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Press file
          - French (Folder 12)
          - Polish (Folder 13)
        - Program (Folder 14)
        - Reports on agricultural conditions in various communist countries (Folder 15)
        - Resolutions (Folder 16)
        - Speeches
          - General (Box 145, Folder 1)
          - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 2)
          - Wilk, F. J. (Folder 3)
          - Wronski, H. (Folder 4)
    - Cooperative Forum, Washington
      - 1950
        - General (Folder 5)
        - Receipts and expenditures (Folder 6)
      - 1952 (Folder 7)
      - 1953
        - General (Folder 8)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 9)
      - 1956 (Folder 10)
  - History
    - Green International - Pre-war period
      - General. Press commentaries, 1920s (Folder 11)
      - "Red and Green: History of International Peasant Union and the Red Communist Peasant Union" by F. J. Wilk, n.d. Mimeograph (Folder 12)
      - "Red Peasant International, Moscow 1923," n.d. Mimeograph (Folder 13)
    - Offices
      - General
        - France (Folder 14)
        - Germany and Austria (Folder 15)
        - Great Britain (Folder 16)
      - Officers (Folder 17)
    - Seminars - Collectivization in Eastern Europe, University of Kentucky, 1955 (Folder 18)
  - Poznan Uprising, 1956
    - General
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Correspondence (Folder 20)
      - I.P.U. Bulletin issues (Folder 21)
      - International press file
        - General (Box 146, Folder 1)
        - French (Folder 2)
        - German (Folder 3)
        - Polish (Folder 4)
      - Speeches and statements by Stanislaw Mikolajczyk
        - General
          - General (Folder 5)
          - List (Folder 6)
          - Notes (Folder 7)
        - France (Folder 8)
        - United States
          - General (Folder 9)
          - "Reflections and Conclusions on the Events in Poland" (Folder 10)
    - Congressional hearings, 1956 August-November (Folder 11)
    - Polska Partia Socjalno-Demokratyczna (Folder 12)
    - Polski Narodowy Komitet Demokratyczny (Folder 13)
    - Polski Ruch Wolnosciowy Niepodleglosc i Demokracja (Folder 14)
    - Polskie Stronnictwo Ludowe (Folder 15)
    - Radio Warszawa, 1956 June-July (Folder 16)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1918-1966
  - American Jewish Committee. See Jews
  - Anders, Wladyslaw
    - General
      - General
        - 1941 (Box 147, Folder 1)
        - 1942 (Folder 2)
        - 1943 (Folder 3)
        - 1954 (Folder 4)
      - Interview, Pravda, 1941 December 4 (Folder 5)
      - Memoirs. Clippings, 1948 (Folder 6)
      - Obituary, 1970 (Folder 7)
      - Printed matter, 1941-1954 (Folder 8)
      - Writings. "Stalin Set Me Free," 1949 (Folder 9)
    - Army
      - General
        - 1941
          - June (Folder 10)
          - August (Folder 11)
          - September (Folder 12)
          - October (Folder 13)
          - November (Folder 14)
          - December (Folder 15)
        - 1942
          - January-March (Folder 16)
          - April-June (Folder 17)
          - July-September (Folder 18)
          - October-December (Folder 19)
        - 1943
          - January-March (Folder 20)
          - July (Folder 21)
          - October (Folder 22)
      - Jewish question
        - 1941
          - August (Folder 23)
          - September (Folder 24)
          - October (Folder 25)
          - November (Folder 26)
          - December (Folder 27)
        - 1942 January-June (Folder 28)
        - 1943 June-September (Folder 29)
    - Financial situation - Availability of funds, 1950 (Folder 30)
    - Kot, Stanislaw. Reports, 1943 (Folder 31)
    - Polish armed forces in the West, 1949-1951 (Folder 32)
    - Sosnkowski, Kazimierz - Commentary on anniversary of German aggression, Völkischer Beobachter, 1943 (Folder 33)
    - Strasburger, Henryk - Situation in army, 1944 (Folder 34)
    - Toth, Jan. Correspondence to Rubin and Wyszynski on arrest of Home Army leaders in 1945, 1965-1966 (Folder 35)
    - Trial, 1959-1960
      - Clippings
        - British press
          - General (Box 148, Folder 1)
          - The Times (Folder 2)
        - French press (Folder 3)
        - Polish émigré
          - General (Folder 4)
          - Orzel Bialy (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence
        - 1956-1959 (Folder 6)
        - 1960 (Folder 7)
        - 1961 (Folder 8)
      - Dossier of Stanislaw Mikolajczyk (Folder 9)
      - List of court documents, "Résumé de L'Affaire," 1961 (Folder 10)
      - Notes (Folder 11)
      - Testimonies
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 12)
        - Modelski, Izydor (Folder 13)
  - Arciszewski, Miroslaw, lecture on Romania, 1938 (Folder 14)
  - Arciszewski, Tomasz, 1944-1945 (Folder 15)
  - Art thefts - Poland, 1942-1943 (Folder 16)
  - Bialer, Seweryn - Defection, 1956 (Folder 17)
  - Bitonski, Adam, Case of, 1961-1964
    - Correspondence (Folder 18)
    - Documents (Folder 19)
    - Notes (Folder 20)
    - Press clippings, 1963
      - English (Folder 21)
      - French (Folder 22)
      - German (Folder 23)
      - Polish émigré (Folder 24)
  - Blodniak, Adolf, 1962 (Folder 25)
  - British Parliamentary Group for World Government. Brochure, 1952 (Folder 26)
  - Catholic Church
    - General, 1918-1939 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Hlond, August (Folder 2)
    - John XXIII - Encyclical "Pacem in Terris." Clippings, 1963 (Folder 3)
    - Millenium celebrations
      - General, 1961-1966 (Folder 4)
      - Printed matter (Folder 5)
    - Paul VI
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Encyclical "Mater et Magistra." Analysis, 1962 (Folder 7)
    - Pius XII
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Letter to Catholics behind the Iron Curtain, 1956 August 29 (Folder 9)
      - Speech, Wolajac o Pokoj nad Swiatem, 1943 June 2 (in Polish) (Folder 10)
    - Poland
      - General. Press clippings, 1946-1953 (Folder 11)
      - Church directory, 1961 (Folder 12)
      - Diplomatic relations with Poland - Possibility of restoration. Secret report, 1956 (Folder 13)
      - State-church relations
        - 1946-1950 (Folder 14)
        - 1951-1953 (Folder 15)
        - 1954-1956 (Folder 16)
        - 1957-1959 (Folder 17)
        - 1961-1964 (Folder 18)
        - 1966 (Folder 19)
      - World War, 1939-1945-Casualties among the Polish clergy, n.d. (Folder 20)
      - Wyszynski, Stefan - Visit to the Vatican, 1957 June. Top secret reports from Polish sources (Folder 21)
    - Vatican Council. Final text, 1964 (Folder 22)
  - Chrusciel, Antoni. Obituary, 1961 (Folder 23)
  - Churchill, Clementine. Biographical sketch, clipping (Folder 24)
  - 1963
  - Ciechanowski, Jan, "Le couloir polonais: Paix ou révision," speech, Paris, 1933. Typescript (Folder 25)
  - Committee on Communist Aggression (Kersten Committee), 1953-1954
    - General (Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (Folder 27)
    - Minutes, 1954 October 22 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (Folder 2)
    - Report, Interim (Folder 3)
    - Testimonies
      - Modelski, Izydor (Folder 4)
      - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw
        - General (Folder 5)
        - Questions for (Folder 6)
      - Paul, Tadeusz (Folder 7)
  - Communists - Poland
    - General
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Biographies of Polish communists (Folder 9)
      - Pamphlets
        - Krajowa Rada Narodowa I Polski Komitet Wyzwolenia Narodowego, London, 1944 (Folder 10)
        - Ukonstytuowania rzadu. Pamphlet, Lublin, 1944 (Folder 11)
    - Banczyk, Stanislaw
      - "Communist Infiltration into Youth Organizations in Poland" (Folder 12)
      - "Komunisci polscy na uslugach Moskwy w latach 1917-1939"
        - English (Folder 13)
        - Polish (Folder 14)
    - Countries and regions
      - Argentina, 1943 (Folder 15)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1943 (Folder 16)
      - Great Britain
        - Komitet Obrony Rzeczpospolitej, Biuletyn, 1944 (Folder 17)
        - Polski Zwiazek Postepowy, 1943-1944 (Folder 18)
      - Middle East (Folder 19)
      - Soviet Union. Wolna Polska, 1943-1944 (Folder 20)
      - United States - Lange, Oskar, 1943-1944 (Folder 21)
    - Polish United Workers Party Congress, Fourth, 1964 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Zwiazek Patriotow Polskich and Polski Komitet Wyzwolenia Narodowego
      - Ministerstwo Informacji I Dokumenatcji, 1943 (Folder 2)
      - Ministerstwo Spraw Wewnetrznych, 1943 (Folder 3)
      - Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych, 1944 (Folder 4)
      - Sztab Naczelnego Wodza
        - 1943 (Folder 5)
        - 1944 (Folder 6)
  - Constitution
    - General
      - 1935 (Folder 7)
      - 1947, Mala Konstytucja (Folder 8)
      - 1952 (Folder 9)
    - Dokumenty Polityczno-Konstytucyjne
      - Index (Folder 10)
      - Nos. 1-58 (Folder 11)
      - Nos. 59-147 (Folder 12)
      - Nos. 148-236 (Folder 13)
  - Diamand, Wladyslaw, "W poszukiwaniu tla, wytycznych I drog polityki zdrowego rozsadku," 1958. Typescript (Folder 14)